backtoschooloutfits.org 2016-10-13

# Privacy – Back to School Outfits

Dear valued reader:

Thank you for your interest in reading our blog at “backtoschooloutfits.org” This page exists to inform you about our policies and practices with regards to your privacy. We use your personal information solely for the purpose of improving our blog. By using our website you agree to the use of this information in accordance with the policy below.

**Log Data**

This blog has no analytics tracking, therefore there is no personal data collection. Because there is no personal data collection, we do not share any information with third parties of any kind.

**Communications**

There is no newsletter signup, therefore we will not use your personal information to contact you. We also will not use your personal information to share marketing or promotional materials with you of any kind.

**Cookies**

Cookies are files we use to optimize your blog experience. They contain small data pockets which may or may not include an anonymous signal unique to your computer. Web sites send cookies to your browser which are then stored on your computer’s hard drive. This site uses cookies to collect information. You can access your browser settings and instruct your browser to refuse to accept cookies, You can also set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer browser. If you choose to disable cookies, some parts of our website may not be accessible to you.

**Security**

Rest assured, the security of your personal information is of the utmost importance to us. While we do not save, store, or distribute your personal information to third parties or use your information for marketing or promotional services, no method of internet security is perfect. We will do everything in our power to ensure the security of your information; however, no guarantees can be made on its complete safety.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

This privacy policy is effective as of September 6, 2016 and is subject to change without notice. This policy will remain effective until such changes are made on future dates. Such changes will be noted immediately in our privacy policy and be posted in place of the current policy. We recommend you check this page periodically to ensure you are up to date on our current policies. Should you continue to use the website after changes are made, said use represents your agreement with the updated policy.

**Contact Us**

Please [contact us](http://backtoschooloutfits.org/contact) with any questions or concerns regarding this policy.
